lfitzgibbons@unomaha.edu

Summary of Qualifications

- Dedicated front-end web developer with 2 years of paid internship experience.
- Adaptive to new and changing technologies.
- Strong analytical and ideation skills for developing and working on projects.
- Excellent research and problem solving abilities.

Core Competencies

Programming Languages

Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C, Pearl, Visual Basic, Objective-C

Integrated Development Environments

Eclipse, Microsoft Visual Studio, NetBeans, Xcode, PHPStorm

Other Technologies

Photoshop, Adobe Creative Suite, Microsoft Office

Education

University of Nebraska – Omaha, Omaha, Nebraska

Peter Kiewit Institute College of Information Science and Technology

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Expected May 2018

- 3.7 GPA
- Walter Scott, Jr. Scholarship Recipient
- Dean's List

Experience

Gallup's Education Taskforce – High School Innovation Program, Gallup June 2014 – August 2014

- Learned key software development skills for the betterment of myself and the company.
- Developed a fully functional web application using RESTful practices
- Designed social media strategies for pulling interest and followers

System's Application Developer Intern, Gallup

October 2014 - Present

- Worked on a shared resource team, assisting with many teams and coworkers.
- Maintained front-end web applications.
- Created a visual design in CSS from scratch, following brand styling guidelines.
- High School Internship Coordinator/Leader GET HIP Program.
- Performed work on 7 major projects and several minor projects.

Additional Information

Aim Achiever
May 2010 – Present

Gallup All Star Award

March 2016